<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on STATCOM at ISU</title>
    <link>https://isu-statcom.netlify.app/categories/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on STATCOM at ISU</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>This website lists content related to talks that have either already taken place or scheduled to take place in the STATCOM organization. All rights remain with the organization respective officers.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://isu-statcom.netlify.app/categories/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Practical Farmers of Iowa</title>
      <link>https://isu-statcom.netlify.app/2020/10/practical-farmers-of-iowa/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://isu-statcom.netlify.app/2020/10/practical-farmers-of-iowa/</guid>
      <description>PFI is a non-profit that works with Iowa farmers. One of the things they do is organize small-scale field trials to study the effects of sustainable agricultural practices. The project requires the following tasks:
Automating the extraction of data from 20+ years of badly formatted records.Data cleaning.Database design.Advice on best-practices for collecting and storing data in ways that make it easy to use for future analysis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ames Public Lirbary Strategic Survey 2020</title>
      <link>https://isu-statcom.netlify.app/2020/05/ames-public-lirbary-strategic-survey-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://isu-statcom.netlify.app/2020/05/ames-public-lirbary-strategic-survey-2020/</guid>
      <description>The 2020 Ames Public Library Strategic survey was administered between June and August of 2020 through an internet form and paper surveys distributed to all city residents in their water bill and at the library. There were responses collected. 189 paper surveys were returned, 42 from the library, and the rest of the surveys were from the online form. The following report presents the results for each question in the survey and some additional analysis of the data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ericson Library Community Survey</title>
      <link>https://isu-statcom.netlify.app/2013/11/ericson-library-community-survey/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://isu-statcom.netlify.app/2013/11/ericson-library-community-survey/</guid>
      <description>The 2018 Ericson Library community survey was administered between June and August of 2018 through an internet form and paper surveys distributed to all city residents in their water bill and at the library. There were 290 responses collected. 189 paper surveys were returned, 42 from the library, and the rest of the surveys were from the online form. The following report presents the results for each question in the survey and some additional analysis of the data.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
