<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>database design on STATCOM at ISU</title>
    <link>https://isu-statcom.netlify.app/tags/database-design/</link>
    <description>Recent content in database design on STATCOM at ISU</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>This website lists content related to talks that have either already taken place or scheduled to take place in the STATCOM organization. All rights remain with the organization respective officers.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://isu-statcom.netlify.app/tags/database-design/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Practical Farmers of Iowa</title>
      <link>https://isu-statcom.netlify.app/2020/10/practical-farmers-of-iowa/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://isu-statcom.netlify.app/2020/10/practical-farmers-of-iowa/</guid>
      <description>PFI is a non-profit that works with Iowa farmers. One of the things they do is organize small-scale field trials to study the effects of sustainable agricultural practices. The project requires the following tasks:
Automating the extraction of data from 20+ years of badly formatted records.Data cleaning.Database design.Advice on best-practices for collecting and storing data in ways that make it easy to use for future analysis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>National Student Exchange Survey Visualization</title>
      <link>https://isu-statcom.netlify.app/2020/02/national-student-exchange-survey-visualization/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://isu-statcom.netlify.app/2020/02/national-student-exchange-survey-visualization/</guid>
      <description>National Student Exchange (NSE) is a non-profit consortium of 165 colleges and universities throughout the United States, Canada, Guam, Puerto Rico, and the U.S. Virgin Islands. NSE provides opportunities for collegiate study away and student exchange among member campuses. NSE recently reached out to Iowa State’s STATCOM chapter for help visualizing survey data. We are hoping to leverage the awesome graphical minds of ISU’s Graphics Group to accomplish two things: (1) have a discussion about visualizing “feedback” survey data, including Likert scale data and qualitative text response data, and (2) have the group spend some time with the data, making visualizations!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
